<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Getting_started on Keydra Documentation</title><link>https://athena-home-loans.github.io/keydra/getting_started/</link><description>Recent content in Getting_started on Keydra Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 14:03:08 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://athena-home-loans.github.io/keydra/getting_started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Initial Bitbucket Setup</title><link>https://athena-home-loans.github.io/keydra/getting_started/bitbucket/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 14:03:08 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://athena-home-loans.github.io/keydra/getting_started/bitbucket/</guid><description>To use Bitbucket for your config source, read on. If needed, you can create a free account here.
Setup a configuration repository Create a new private repository in Bitbucket. Let&amp;rsquo;s call it KeydraConfiguration. Clone your new repo locally. Click the Clone button at the top right of your new repo&amp;rsquo;s Source page, and paste into your terminal.
Note: You may need to setup an SSH key for this, see here for help if needed.</description></item><item><title>Initial Github Setup</title><link>https://athena-home-loans.github.io/keydra/getting_started/github/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 14:03:08 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://athena-home-loans.github.io/keydra/getting_started/github/</guid><description>To use Github for your config source, read on.
Setup a configuration repository Create a new private repository in Github. Let&amp;rsquo;s call it KeydraConfiguration.
Clone your new repo locally. Click the Clone button in your new repo, and paste into your terminal.
git clone git@github.com:&amp;lt;your Github org or username&amp;gt;/keydraconfiguration.git cd keydraconfiguration Create a Personal Access Token From your repository in your browser, click Settings from your profile avatar in the top right corner.</description></item><item><title>Initial Gitlab Setup</title><link>https://athena-home-loans.github.io/keydra/getting_started/gitlab/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 14:03:08 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://athena-home-loans.github.io/keydra/getting_started/gitlab/</guid><description>To use Gitlab as your config source, read on.
Setup a configuration repository Create a new repository in Gitlab. Let&amp;rsquo;s call it KeydraConfiguration.
Clone your new repo locally.
Create a Personal Access Token Follow the instructions to create a personal access token. https://docs.gitlab.com/ee/user/profile/personal_access_tokens.html
Log into to the AWS Console and navigate to the Secrets Manager service.
Click the orange Store a new secret button.
Choose a secret type of Other type of secrets, and add a plaintext secret as follows (substituting your details).</description></item></channel></rss>